atbatt.com 2015-11-08

# Privacy Policy

Home / About Us / Privacy Policy

At Battery Company, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personally identifiable information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, www.atbatt.com and does not cover information that may be collected behind the log in on our website. 

This privacy statement covers the Web site [www.atbatt.com](http://www.atbatt.com/). Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact our Customer Service Department. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). 

Atbatt.com is operated by At Battery Company, Inc. We respect the privacy of users who visit this Site. We are committed to keeping your personally identifiable information private and secure. By accessing this Site and using the services we provide, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

 **Changes In The Privacy Policy  **

This Privacy Policy will change from time to time to reflect changes in how we do business and changes in services available to you through our Site. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. We show the last updated date at the beginning of the Privacy Policy. The use of your information is subject to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use in effect at the time of use. You may access the current Privacy Policy at any time by clicking on the "Privacy Policy" link on our home page. 

 **Log Files.**  You may visit our Site anonymously, without revealing any information about yourself. Our servers may track and collect the domain names and IP addresses of visitors by the use of log files and this information may be used to measure how visitors use our Site. We use this information, which may include the number of visitors, the average time spent on the Site, the pages viewed, etc., to improve the content we offer. This information does not personally identify any site visitor and aggregate data may be shared with third parties to improve our Site and its contents. Log Files are not tied to personally identifiable information. 

 **Personally Identifiable Information.**  When you make a purchase from our site you can choose to open an account, which will allow you to store your billing and shipping information on our servers or you can check out without opening an account. If you choose to set up an account you will provide your name, email address, credit card information, address, and phone number and will select a password. After you set up your account, the next time you enter our Site you can log in by entering your email address and password and your billing and shipping information is automatically completed. We do not store your credit card number for your security. Whether you open an account or not, on checkout you can sign up to receive our newsletter to keep you informed about our latest offers, current promotions, specials and new additions to the Atbatt.com site. See Choice/Opt-out below to learn how you may change your preferences. If you send us an email through the "Contact Us" page, we use your email address to respond to your question. We do not save the address of emails we receive after we have responded. If you choose to shop without opening an account your information will be retained only as long as needed to process and fulfill your order, in most cases it is deleted after three months. 

 **How we use your personally identifiable information.**  We use the information you provide when shopping on our Site to process your orders, to keep you updated on your orders and to personalize your shopping experience. In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by reputable third-party banking and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card and to process your order. They are under contractual obligation to keep your personally identifiable information private and are not permitted to use or share your information for their own purposes including marketing. We use your email address to send you our newsletters if you ask to be placed on our list. We may share aggregated statistics not linked to any individual about buying patterns, sales and other shopping information with our marketing partners. 

 **Tell-A-Friend.**  If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. At Battery Company, Inc. does store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

 **Security.**  Our secure servers protect sensitive data including your credit card information using SSL encryption and firewall technology to protect your personally identifiable information from being read as it travels to our ordering system. Information sent to us by email is not encrypted and is therefore not secure. While we take reasonable measures to prevent the loss or misuse of the information that you provide to us, including but not limited to, your Personally Identifiable Information, due to factors beyond our control, we do not guarantee that your Personally Identifiable Information or any other information collected by us will be completely secure from misappropriation by hackers or other third parties or from other criminal activities. 

 **Sharing Personally Identifiable Information.**  We are not in the business of selling, renting or sharing your Personally Identifiable Information to or with others except our agents and service providers and as described in this privacy policy. We do not share your personally identifiable information with any third party for their own marketing purposes. 

We do not reveal Personally Identifiable Information about you to unaffiliated third parties, unless: (1) you request or authorize it; (2) the information is provided to a service provider to help complete a transaction for you; (3) the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); or (5) the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, etc.). Atbatt.com fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. 

 **Service Providers.**  We use other third parties to provide shipping and credit card processing services on our site. When you purchase a product(s) on our site, we will share your contact, shipping and credit card information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose including their own marketing purposes. 

FedEx Corporation  
942 South Shady Grove Road  
Memphis, TN 38120  
1-800-GO-FEDEX  
[www.fedex.com](http://www.fedex.com/) | UPS Corporate Headquarters  
55 Glenlake Parkway, NE  
Atlanta , GA 30328  
United States  
[www.ups.com](http://www.ups.com/) | US Postal Service Headquarters  
475 L'Enfant Plaza, SW  
Washington DC  
1-800-ASK-USPS  
---|---|---  
  
**Cookies.**  A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. 

Like most websites, we use "cookies" to keep track of your current shopping session, to personalize your experience and so that you may retrieve your shopping cart at any time. However, we do NOT use cookies to examine your surfing behavior before or after you leave our Site. There are products commercially available that are designed to help you disable cookies. Although we want you to be aware that such products exist, please note that if you choose to use them we will not be able to provide you with a personalized service, and it may result in certain features and services not being available to you. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. It is used solely for purposes of processing your order and is not shared with any third parties. 

 **Flash LSOs.**  We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or high game score, or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information. 

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118>

**3rd Party Tracking.**  The use of cookies by our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] is/is not covered by our privacy policy. We do/do not have access or control over these cookies. Our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] use session ID cookies [to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc.] 

Our third party partners employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do [not] tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personally identifiable information. 

 **Gift Certificates.**  If you purchase a gift certificate from our site, you will give us the recipient's name and email address if you wish to send the certificate by email. If you wish to send a certificate by regular mail, you will give us the name, mailing information and phone number for the recipient. The recipient information you give us will only be used to send the gift certificate and for no other purpose. It will be deleted from our servers in most cases after three months. 

 **Child Privacy.**  Because of the nature of our business, our products and services are not designed to appeal to children, and therefore we do not knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from children. Our terms and conditions of use require that any registration may only be made by those over the age of 16. By using our services, you are representing that you are at least 16 years of age or have the permission from a parent or legal guardian to use our service. If we know that information is being provided by a child under the age of 16, then we will not collect the information without parental consent or parent notification, which will include the opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information or to prevent the child's participation in the activity. Without parental consent, online information will only be used to respond to an unsolicited request and for no other purposes. We recognize that protecting children's identities and privacy online is important and that the responsibility to do so rests with both the online industry and with parents. 

We encourage parents or guardians to monitor the use of this Site by children to insure that they are not exposed to material that the parent or guardian may find objectionable. Parents are also encouraged to use parental control capabilities within their internet software to assist in their efforts to limit access to certain sites. 

Access to Your Information: To access your account information go to "My Account" to view orders, change passwords, change or remove account information. If you have any issues accessing this information please contact us at 1-877-528-2288. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

Choice/Opt-out: You may change any of your personally identifiable information in your account on-line at any time by clicking on the "My Account" link on the home page. You may change or remove your email address from our mailing list or to cancel your account or change your receipt of our newsletter by emailing theCustomer Service Departmentand placing "Unsubscribe" in the subject matter line, or by calling our Customer Service Representative toll-free at 1-877-528-2288. 

 **Surveys or Contests**. From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name, email address and/or shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We use this information collected to notify contest winners and award prizes. In addition, our monthly contests will require you to submit your email address and by giving us your email address you agree to receive 2 promotional emails a month in exchange for an opportunity to win that month’s particular prize. If you would like to be removed from the monthly contest and not receive our promotional emails, please follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each email. 

 **Blogs/ Forums.**  Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, Contact Us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

 **Linked Sites or Other Parties:**  Atbatt.com's Site may contain links to other sites owned or operated by third parties. This Privacy Policy only addresses Atbatt.com's use and disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Site. While we try to link only to sites that share our standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties or the content of linked sites, although we do encourage you to read the applicable privacy policies and terms and conditions of such parties or web sites. 

By choosing to visit our Site you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use (incorporated herein by reference) or any other agreement we have with you, will be governed by the law of the State of California. In the event of any conflict between the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, then the Terms of Use shall control. Any dispute regarding our Privacy Policy will be submitted to TRUSTe's Watchdog Resolution Dispute Program (WDR). By using this site you also agree to arbitrate all other disputes (including disputes finally resolved through WDR) and to abide by any limitation on damages contained in our Terms of Use or other agreement we have with you. 

 **Contacting Us:**  If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, would like more information, or if you believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please Contact Us or write to: 

At Battery Company, Inc.  
28918 Hancock Parkway  
Valencia, CA 91355  
United States

Copyright © 2014 At Battery Company. All Rights Reserved.
